gontry.com 2013-06-05

# Gontry - Privacy Policies

  |   |   | 

##  GONTRY.COM - PRIVACY POLICY 

Latest Revised on: May 06, 2009 

**About Gontry.com**

At Gontry.com we recognize that privacy is important. This Policy applies to all of the products, services and information offered by gontry.com or its subsidiaries. 

#### Information we collect and how we use it

We offer a number of services that do not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us, such as recipes,nightlife,restaurants etc. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information 

#### Information you provide

When you sign up for a Gontry Account, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). 

#### Gontry.com cookies

When you visit Gontry.com, we send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people search. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Gontry features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 

#### Log information

When you use Gontry services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

#### User communications

When you send email or other communication to Gontry.com, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

#### Other sites 

This Privacy Policy applies to web sites and services that are owned and operated by Gontry.com. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. 

Gontry.com only processes personal information for the purposes described in the applicable Privacy Policy and/or privacy notice for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include: 

  * **Choices for personal information** When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. 
  * If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent. You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case Gontry.com may not be able to provide those services to you. 
  * **Information security** We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 
  * We restrict access to personal information to Gontry.com employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 
  * **Data integrity** Gontry.com processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 
  * **Accessing and updating personal information** When you use Gontry.com services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Some of our services have different procedures to access, correct or delete users'personal information. We provide the details for these procedures in the specific privacy notices or FAQs for these services. 
  * **Enforcement** Gontry.com regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or Gontry.com treatment of personal information by contacting us through this web site When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is Gontry.com policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Gontry.com and an individual.
  * **Changes to this policy** Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will try not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes). 

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this web site.
